AJMAL JALAL FULL STACK WFB DEVELOPER II WORK AUTHORIZED-NO VISA SPONSORSHIP NEEDED

Projects

lshiftr **July 2018 to Aug. 2018**

Ishiftr is an automatic shift scheduling and schedule assignment platform that helps employers enhance their performance and keep track of the employees easily. It was a group project where I worked equally on the back and front end. The utilized technologies are Node.js, Express, MongoDB, React, Bootstrap, Reactstrap and Stripe.

Lambda Notes March 2018 to Current

Lambda Notes is a note taking app with smart functionalities like sending notes directly to email or as a text message to mobile. Node, Express, MongoDB, React, Redux and Bootstrap are used to build this amazing app.

Experience

Lambda School California Feb. 2018 to Current Web Developer

Computer Science & Software Engineering Academy that provides an immersive hands-on curriculum with a focus on computer science, software engineering, and web development.

- Approached all coding challenges using pair programming
- Utilized agile software development and Git workflow on all projects
- Hands on experience with client and server testing,
- Completed all curriculum course work including; React, react native, redux, node, express, mongoDB, mocha, chai etc...

Joint Anti-Corruption Monitoring and Evaluation Committee Afghanistan

Senior Research Officer

Strategy

July 2017 to Oct. 2017 Wrote an analyze on the newly drafted Afghanistan's Anti-corruption

Kabul.

 Led 2 vulnerabilities to corruption assessment projects in the Ministry of Religious Affairs and the Ministry of Mines

Afghanistan Independent Defenders (AID)

Head of Training Department

Kabul. Afghanistan Aug. 2015 to Feb. 2016

- Established a practical training course for attorneys for the first time in Afghanistan in coordination with the Afghanistan Independent Bar Association
- Trained 60 attorneys on practical legal skills
- Developed 10 training manuals

Max Planck Institute for Comparative Public Law and International Law

Project Assistant and Researcher

Afghanistan Feb. 2011 to Sept. 2012

Kabul.

• Conducted 5 training workshops for judges, prosecutors, and attorneys in

- different cities
- Edited administrative law manual
- Translated legal texts from English to Farsi and vise versa

Contact

🕶 ajmaljalal58@gmail.com

9163456008

♥ Sacramento, CA

in ajmaljalal/

Aimalialal

Education

Pettit College of Law. ONU

Feb. 2016 to May 2017

Master of Laws (LL.M)

Andolu University. Turkev

Oct. 2012 to June 2015

Master of Arts (MA) Public Law

Kabul University, March 2007 to Dec. 2010 Afghanistan

Bachelors of Arts (BA) Law and Political Sciences

Skills

MERN STACK

JavaScript

Node.is

Express.js

React.is

Redux

MongoDB

Bootstrap

Materialize CSS

Strip.is

Mocha

Chai